Guide to the Oversize Manuscripts Collection 1648-2018 MS OS
New-York Historical Society
- Series II. Oversize Manuscripts From Other Collections, 1714-2018
  - [Y-Taylor, Jack papers (MS 3150)] Tammany Hall (2 folders), 2014-2016, n.d. (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Thursby, Emma. Papers] Documents, 1802-1909 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Tulchin, David papers regarding the 77th Division "Lost Battalion"], 1939 September 24 (Oversize large)
    Group photograph taken at a reunion of the Lost Battalion Survivors, New York City. A stickie note attached to the photo when donated to N-YHS identified David Tulchin as in the front row, 4th from the left. For the rest of the collection, see the Guide to the David Tulchin Papers Regarding the 77th Division "Lost Battalion," 1918-1972 (MS 3155).
  - [Y-Ulster County, N.Y.], 1676-1730 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Ulster County, N.Y.], 1710-1750 (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Ulster County, N.Y.], 1719 (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Ulster County, N.Y.], 1719-1721 (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Ulster County, N.Y.], 1720 July 7 (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Ulster County, N.Y.], 1720 July 7 (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Ulster County, N.Y.], 1720 July 7 (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Ulster County, N.Y.], 1739-1759 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Ulster County, N.Y.], 1750 (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Ulster County, N.Y.], 1759 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Ulster County, N.Y.], 1762-1814 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Ulster County, N.Y.], 1778 (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Van Cortlandt Papers] Inheritance- Peter and Cornelia Van Dyck, 1719 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Van Ness-Philip Papers] Appointments, 1905-1930 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Van Ness-Philip Papers] Certificates, 1856-1938 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Van Ness-Philip Papers] Certificates, Photographs, Map, 1876-1935 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Van Renssalaer] Van Renssalaer Manor/Watervlidt, ca 1863 (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Walton Family], 1704-1804 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Walton Family], 1707-1798 (Oversize medium)
  - [Y-Walton Family], 1708 April 22 (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Walton Family], 1720-1806 (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Walton Family], 1768 (Oversize large)
  - [Y-Washington Arch, MS 443.30], undated (Oversize medium)
    Tracing paper plan of reviewing stands for dedication ceremony. See finding aid for Washington Arch records, MS 443.30
  - [Y-Webb, George Creighton] Silver Star for Gallantry, 1918 July 9 (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Whelpley, Abigail Belden. MS 3067], 1824 (Oversize small)
    Indenture. See Abigail Belden Whelpley papers finding aid for detail.
  - [Y-White, Richard Grant] Sheet Music, Undated (Oversize small)
  - [Y-White, Richard Grant] Sheet Music, Undated (Oversize small)
  - [Y-Wright, Helen Martha] Indentures, 1774-1846 (Oversize medium)
    see finding aid for MS 3111 Helen Martha Wright papers